<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<elements>
	<info>
		<name>Items</name>
		<update version="0.0.34">
			<file name="items.xml" url="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Aeondromach/aeondroDND/main/Aeondromach/Kalgorath/items.xml" />
		</update>
	</info>

    <element name="Anterius Potion" type="Magic Item" source="Magnus" id="ID_POTIONS_">
            <description>
                <p>The Anterius Potion is a very rare elixir of rare potency, crafted from ten nearly unattainable ingredients, each harvested from distant corners of the world. Its creation is shrouded in secrecy, known only to the most skilled alchemists, and even they whisper of the great difficulty in obtaining its components—be it the heart of a celestial flower that blooms once every century, or the tears of a forgotten deity locked in ancient stone.</p>

    <p>The potion itself is a translucent black liquid, with a shining pink epicenter, remnant that of a galaxy, with specks of legendary ingredients, reminding that of home among the heavens.</p>

    <p>The Anterius Potion is most famous for its unique purpose: to suppress the effects of the infamous Nephalem's Rot, a disease capable of corrupting even the purest of celestial beings. While the potion cannot cure the curse, it serves as a powerful medicine, halting the spread of the ailment and preventing it from claiming the life of the infected angel. However, the potion’s effects are temporary, meaning the afflicted must seek continual doses—each more difficult to obtain than the last—to stave off the curse’s deadly embrace.</p>

    <p>Its rarity and life-saving power make the Anterius Potion one of the most sought-after and coveted substances in existence, often the subject of wars, bargains, and very rare quests.</p>

    <p>You also regain 1hp upon consumption.</p>
		</description>
		<setters>
			<set name="category">Potions</set>
			<set name="weight" lb="0.5">½ lb.</set>
			<set name="cost" currency="gp">3</set>
			<set name="type">Potion</set>
			<set name="rarity">Very Rare</set>
			<set name="stackable">true</set>
		</setters>
	</element>

	<element name="Ætorii Amulet (Faded)" type="Magic Item" source="Magnus" id="ID_MAGIC_ITEM_AETORII_AMULET_FADED">
		<description>
			<p>A small silver amulet, circular in shape, with a diamond embezzeled into the center. Once of legendary power, capable of stopping even the most destructive of curses, now the amulet sits, Faded of it's unique power.</p>
		</description>
		<setters>
			<set name="category">Wondrous Items</set>
			<set name="cost" currency="gp">0</set>
			<set name="weight" lb="0">0 lb.</set>
			<set name="type">Wondrous Item</set>
			<set name="rarity">Common</set>
			<set name="attunement">true</set>
		</setters>
	</element>

	<element name="Infernal Stone" type="Magic Item" source="Magnus" id="ID_MAGIC_ITEM_INFERNAL_STONE">
		<description>
			<p>A strange rough black stone found in The Ward, inscribed with a glowing green rune, in the shape of a singular vertical scratch mark, 4 diagonal smaller scratches going down the first mark, all encompassed by a ovular mark. After some work, discovered to be of Infernal origins. Stone appears to forcefully change the user's mind, corrupting it.</p>

			<p>Found off of a carriage driver, after it corrupted him, claimed it was supposed to protect him from death.</p>
		</description>
		<setters>
			<set name="category">Wondrous Items</set>
			<set name="cost" currency="gp">0</set>
			<set name="weight" lb="0">0 lb.</set>
			<set name="type">Wondrous Item</set>
			<set name="rarity">???</set>
			<set name="attunement">false</set>
		</setters>
	</element>
</elements>
